hi everyone and welcome to the brand-new
大家好，欢迎来到全新的
Cole FX youtube channel my name is
YouTube频道Cole FX我的名字是
Nikhil epilogue and in this channel I
Nikhil的结语，在这个频道中
discuss software development in general
一般讨论软件开发
with particular focus on the JVM and on
特别关注JVM和
Java today is a special day though
今天的Java是特别的一天
because we're having a job and I work a
因为我们正在工作，而我
party Java 9 is out today and if you are
派对Java 9今天发布，如果您在
following me on Twitter or reading my
在Twitter上关注我或阅读我的
blog you already know what I think about
您已经知道我的想法的博客
it so to kick off this YouTube channel I
因此，我开始了这个YouTube频道
decided to ask other members of the Java
决定问Java的其他成员
community what they think about the new
他们对新的想法
release without further ado let's meet
事不宜迟地发布，让我们见面
the panel hi i'm simon maple the
嗨，我是西蒙·枫
director of developer advocacy at zero
开发者倡导总监为零
turnaround hi there i'm steven kolb or
你好，我是史蒂文·科尔布
engineering leader type and gamma and
工程负责人类型和伽玛
creative the jato projects hi my name is
创意jato项目嗨，我叫
Christian Spain and I'm a member of the
基督教西班牙，我是
JUnit five core team hi I'm Nicola I'm a
JUnit五个核心团队您好，我是Nicola，我是
Java developer author and trainer at
Java开发人员作者兼培训师
core effects hi I'm Trisha I'm a
核心效果，嗨，我是Trisha，我是
developer advocate for JetBrains hi i'm
JetBrains的开发倡导者您好，我是
christine lagarde I'm working phrase
克里斯汀·拉加德我正在用短语
cast as the manager of developer
担任开发人员经理
relations hi my name is sunny monkey and
关系，我的名字是阳光明媚的猴子，
I'm a fellow a Software Architect at
我是一名软件架构师
luminous in the Netherlands and author
在荷兰发光，作者
of the Oh Ronnie butch a phenomenal
哦，罗尼·巴奇
arity yeah my name is Ian Sheldon
我是伊恩·谢尔顿（Ian Sheldon）
software developer working with a spring
弹簧工作的软件开发人员
data team of pivotal hi I'm Marco
关键数据团队我是Marco
Beckwith I'm a manager on time
Beckwith我是准时的经理
performance person I have a consultancy
我有咨询服务的表演者
called code Karim LLC hello my name is
叫代码Karim LLC你好，我叫
Rafael I'm open source author of flavors
我是Rafael的开放源代码作者
like fight buddy I'm also very own
像哥们一样，我也很属于自己
mojito and not on that I'm consultancy
莫吉托，而不是我是顾问
and Oslo
和奥斯陆
my name is Wayne Beaton I'm the director
我叫Wayne Beaton我是导演
of open source projects at the Eclipse
Eclipse上的开源项目
Foundation
基础
I represent the approximate 300 open
我代表大约300开放
source projects hosted by the Eclipse
Eclipse托管的源项目
Foundation that cover all sorts of
涵盖各种基础的
technology areas hello my name is Simon
技术领域你好，我叫西蒙
Mercer and I work as the deputy CTO at
我和美世（Mercer）担任副首席技术官
Azul systems welcome ladies and
Azul系统欢迎女士们和
gentlemen and thank you very much for
先生们，非常感谢你
being part of this video if you're
如果你是这个视频的一部分
interested to learn more about these
有兴趣了解更多有关这些的信息
Java experts or the projects they
Java专家或他们的项目
mentioned check out the description box
提到检查出描述框
which is full of useful links and while
其中充满了有用的链接，而
you're down there hit the subscribe
你在那儿打了订阅
button so you don't miss any of my other
按钮，这样您就不会错过我的其他任何人
videos I asked each of my guests the
我问每位客人的影片
same questions what is your favorite
同样的问题，你最喜欢什么
Java line feature what impact my job and
Java系列功能对我的工作有何影响，
I have on your project what impact my
我对您的项目有什么影响
java line have
java行有
the wider community what are some good
更广泛的社区有什么好处
sources to learn on the new release we
在新版本中学习的资源我们
go through these questions one by one
一步一步地解决这些问题
and I can't wait to hear the answers
我等不及要听答案了
we'll end with a round of applause for
我们以掌声结束
the JDK team with all of that said lot
JDK团队说了很多
let's get it on
让我们继续
Java 9 is packed with features even
Java 9甚至包含许多功能
beyond the module system here are the
除了模块系统，这里还有
panels favorites for me the features
面板最喜欢我的功能
which make Java 9 interesting the API
使Java 9有趣的API
language changes the changes that have
语言改变了已经发生的改变
been made to the streams API the changes
对流API进行了更改
that have been made to the factory
出厂的
methods the initializers of collections
方法的初始值设定项
it's all these little changes to the API
所有这些对API的微小更改
which make java easier and nicer to
这使得Java更加容易和友好
develop with like you know the new the
像你知道的新发展
new process handling api these are the
新流程处理api这些是
pieces of java 9 which i think are most
我认为最多的Java 9件
interesting so besides the new module
有趣，所以除了新模块
system in java 9 i'm also looking
Java 9中的系统我也在寻找
forward to a private method on
转发到一种私有方法
interfaces
介面
we've been added being able to add
我们已经添加了能够添加
static method and default methods in
静态方法和默认方法
Java 8 but private methods will help
Java 8，但是私有方法会有所帮助
additionally with our design features
此外，我们的设计特色
plus also collection factories so you
再加上收集工厂，所以你
also be able to do lists of set of and
也可以做一组和的列表
mapped of which will be great for
映射将非常适合
shortening arcade I feature I'm looking
我正在寻找的缩短街机
forward to our the collection factory
转发到我们的收藏工厂
methods the Java 9 feature I'm looking
我正在寻找的Java 9功能的方法
forward to the most the strong
向最强者前进
capsulation
封装
the number of times I have thought damn
我以为该死的次数
I wish I wouldn't have to make this type
我希望我不必做这种类型
public but there's just no other choice
公开，但别无选择
you know there's another choice I could
你知道我还有另一种选择
just make in public and not export the
只是公开而不是出口
package I think I will use that a lot
包装我想我会经常使用
I'm really looking forward to that
我真的很期待
I think the Java now feature I'm going
我认为我现在要使用Java功能
to use most is the factory methods for
使用最多的是工厂方法
collections this might seem like a
集合可能看起来像一个
really small change to the language but
语言变化很小，但是
it's just going to make my life a lot
这只会让我的生活很多
easier for the sorts of code that I
简化我的各种代码
write all the time I think most mostly
我认为大部分时间都写
I'm looking forward to the sec walking
我期待第二次走
api because that is really interesting
api，因为这真的很有趣
so far you had to either create an
到目前为止，您必须创建一个
exception to get the stack or you have
获取堆栈的异常或您有
to use submit we're at internal api's
使用提交我们在内部api
but all of those things were eager so
但是所有这些事情都渴望
they created the whole stack and if you
他们创建了整个堆栈，如果您
just needed one or two frames that was
只需要一两个框架
not possible so that is that is really
不可能，那是真的
interesting and one feature which is
有趣和一个功能是
unfortunately just experimental ASP HTTP
不幸的是，实验性的ASP HTTP
to client I think that doesn't need any
对客户来说，我认为不需要
explanation
说明
I'm looking forward to seeing how Javon
我很期待看到Javon
inés flagship feature the module system
inés旗舰功能模块系统
will do in the real world I believe
我相信在现实世界中会做到
modularity is one of the most important
模块化是最重要的之一
architectural principles in software
软件中的架构原则
development but it will take time for
发展，但需要时间
people to grasp and embrace modules
人们掌握并拥抱模块
strong encapsulation and explicit
强大的封装和显式
dependencies will change the way your
依赖关系将改变您的方式
coding and design the one thing I'm
编码和设计我自己的一件事
really looking forward to are the
真的很期待
additions to the API of optionals one of
可选API的附加功能之一
my favorite is the contended locking
我最喜欢的是竞争锁
optimization that I usually give talks
我通常讲的优化
on but also there is the string density
上还有弦密度
project which has been in the works for
正在进行的项目
a couple of years now
几年了
I think var handles are very good new
我认为var手柄非常好
feature for handles are basically
手柄的功能基本上是
exposing direct memory access and
公开直接内存访问和
low-level functionality to Java
Java的低级功能
libraries and until now this was often
图书馆，直到现在这经常
you yourself by using unsafe API slyke's
您自己使用不安全的API slyke
on msconfig and this is a very important
在msconfig上，这是非常重要的
step in the direction of exposing this
朝着揭露这个方向
feature and on a standardized manner I
特征和标准化的方式
have two features I particularly like in
有两个我特别喜欢的功能
jk9 both of them are actually very small
jk9他们实际上都很小
the first one isn't really even part of
第一个甚至不是其中的一部分
the job language the libraries or the
图书馆或图书馆的工作语言
java virtual machine
Java虚拟机
what it is is the fact we now have
这就是我们现在拥有的事实
searchable documentation and go to Java
可搜索的文档并转到Java
Docs and if you need something like
文件，如果您需要类似
string builder or something like that
字符串生成器或类似的东西
you don't have to scroll all the way
您不必一直滚动
down to string builder you can just type
到字符串生成器，您只需键入
it into the search bar and that I find
它进入搜索栏，我发现
is unbelievably useful how it's taking
令人难以置信的有用
this 22 years to get to that I don't
这22年来，我不会
quite know the other feature that
非常了解其他功能
particularly like I I noticed this the
特别是像我注意到这个
other day when I wanted to use it it
前几天我想使用它
wasn't there in JDK 8 or is the
在JDK 8中不存在或者是
effectively final variables being used
有效地使用最终变量
in a try with resources block so now you
尝试使用资源块，所以现在您
can use a variable that's outside of the
可以使用不在
trial with the resources block without
在没有资源块的情况下进行试用
having to assign it to a new variable
必须将其分配给新变量
name and I find that it could be very
名字，我发现这可能非常
useful as well Wow people really like
很有用哇人们真的很喜欢
collection factories is it your favorite
收藏工厂是您的最爱
to let me know in the poll we all know
让我在民意测验中知道
that Java line brings more than just new
Java系列带来的不仅仅是新事物
toys to play with though many projects
玩具虽然有很多项目
require some cleanup to properly
需要一些清理才能正确
function the new release and I wanted to
运行新版本，我想
know for my guests whether their
为我的客人知道他们是否
projects are infected too
项目也被感染
so house Java nine go to effects Jay
所以家Java九去效果杰
rebel well one of the key parts of Java
很好地反叛了Java的关键部分之一
9 is the jigsaw module system and those
9是拼图模块系统和那些
of you who are familiar with durable
你们当中那些熟悉耐用性的人
it's a it's a tool that allows job
这是一个允许工作的工具
classes and resources to be reloaded now
现在要重新加载的课程和资源
before Java nine a lot of that is going
在Java之前的九个阶段
to be done with well pretty much all
几乎可以完成所有事情
going to be done with class class and
将与类class和
class loaders it's pretty much
类加载器
terrible's bread and butter but with
糟糕的面包和黄油，但是
Java nine we're introducing an entire
Java 9我们将介绍整个
new module system with you know a module
您知道新模块系统的模块
path which is going to be determined by
路径将由
each each module the scope is going to
范围将涉及的每个模块
determine by each module so depending on
由每个模块确定，因此取决于
what's visible to other modules will be
其他模块可见的是
determined by the module pop module info
由模块弹出模块信息确定
dot Java so we need to understand the
点Java，因此我们需要了解
module in for Java we need to better
Java模块，我们需要更好
reload the module in front or Java as
将模块重新加载到前端或Java中
well as classes that are on the module
以及模块上的类
path so Java nine will have a relatively
Java 9的相对路径
small impact on our particular on our
对我们的特殊影响很小
projects mostly because we're probably
项目主要是因为我们可能
going to need to stick with Java rate
需要坚持使用Java率
for the insurer the short term but we
对于保险公司而言，短期而言，但我们
will be looking to add module info to
将寻求添加模块信息到
our open source projects just just if
我们的开源项目
people want to use them on Java nine
人们想在Java 9上使用它们
it's best to have module info there if
最好在这里有模块信息
we can integrating Java nine modules in
我们可以在其中集成Java 9个模块
the process of final test classes or
期末考试课程的过程或
your module of projects as an ongoing
您正在进行的项目模块
task we are still exploring the best way
我们仍在探索最佳方法的任务
to handle it
处理它
I have already tried that Java 9 on a
我已经在Java 9上尝试过
small microservices application that I
我的小型微服务应用程序
wrote a little while ago I found that
前一阵子我发现
jigsaw was really useful for servicing
拼图对于维修非常有用
some of the design concerns that I don't
我不关心的一些设计问题
normally think about that much in terms
通常要考虑很多
of obviously modularity encapsulation
明显的模块化封装
which bits of the code I want to expose
我想公开哪些代码
and which bits I want to hide
我想隐藏哪些位
I found that overall it made my code
我发现总体来说，这就是我的代码
cleaner and better designed I think the
更干净，设计更好的我认为
the biggest part will be the
最大的部分将是
modernization so we need to make sure
现代化，所以我们需要确保
that his cast works flawlessly with with
与他的演员完美搭配
Java 9 and and the module system
Java 9和模块系统
activated my current projects is OSGi
激活我当前的项目是OSGi
based and I fully expected to remain
基于，我完全希望保留
that way even with a Java 9 module
即使使用Java 9模块也是如此
system in place getting the application
系统就位获取应用程序
to run on the Java 9 class path involves
在Java 9类路径上运行涉及
teasing out some problems with libraries
调解图书馆的一些问题
that
那
rules and abuse ADK insurance I expect
规则和滥用我期望的ADK保险
this to be an exercise that many people
这是很多人的练习
will go through after Jeff and I release
杰夫和我释放后将会经历
actually it was one of my tasks and not
实际上这是我的任务之一，而不是
my favorite task to check what happens
我最喜欢的任务，以检查发生了什么
if people try spring data with Java 9
如果人们使用Java 9尝试Spring数据
and the fun part is there were like two
最有趣的部分是有两个
things that broke due to the module
由于模块损坏的东西
system in spring data itself we fixed
我们在 spring data 本身中修复了系统
that so we are fine well now I don't
这样我们现在很好，我不
think it's gonna be a big impact
认为这会带来很大的影响
latest changes with allowing access of
允许访问的最新更改
the legal access for example don't
例如合法访问
really break anything anymore we on the
真的打破了一切，我们在
path to moving features oh and mostly
运动特征的途径
updating libraries because it's where
更新库，因为它在那里
the breakage happens most of the time so
破损大部分时间都在发生
so our code is not affected that much
因此我们的代码不会受到太大影响
since we're not using many
因为我们没有用很多
unstandardized features in our code for
我们代码中的非标准化功能
Eclipse projects the impact of JAF and 9
Eclipse预测JAF和9的影响
has been happening for a while our
已经有一段时间了
compiler team has to implement based on
编译器团队必须基于
a specification not on the
规格不在
implementation in open JDK so they've
在开放式JDK中实施，因此他们已经
been working with Mark Reinholds team to
与Mark Reinholds团队合作
clarify aspects of the spec the Eclipse
阐明Eclipse规范的各个方面
Java development team has put a
Java开发团队已经将
considerable amount of effort into
投入大量精力
updates to the Eclipse compiler for Java
Eclipse的Java编译器更新
to support Java 9 ecj is an independent
支持Java 9 ecj是独立的
and fully open source implementation of
并完全开源实现
the Java compiler of course these
这些当然是Java编译器
compiler updates feed into the Eclipse
编译器更新馈入Eclipse
IDE support for Java 9 updates to the
IDE对Java 9的更新支持
web tools support and a lot more as you
网络工具支持以及您的更多支持
move forward our projects that produce
推进我们产生的项目
libraries like Eclipse collections or
Eclipse集合之类的库或
Eclipse link are going to have to decide
Eclipse链接将不得不决定
whether or not they'll provide their
他们是否会提供他们的
code as proper modules I'm looking
代码作为我正在寻找的适当模块
forward to the first release of the new
前进到新的第一版
Eclipse open j9 project which implements
Eclipse open j9项目实现
a JVM for the java language that
Java语言的JVM
supports Java 9 well have to say that
支持Java 9的人不得不说
for me personally we don't really have a
就我个人而言，我们真的没有
project that we work on we develop JVM
我们致力于开发JVM的项目
so from our point of view at is all JDK
所以从我们的角度来看，所有JDK
9 means that we release a new version
9表示我们发布了一个新版本
sulu based on the open JDK source code
sulu基于开放的JDK源代码
and we will release a new version of
我们将发布新版本的
commercial JVM with low latency garbage
低延迟垃圾的商业JVM
collection and a faster JIT compiler and
收集和更快的JIT编译器，以及
we'll do that for jdk as 9jk 9 as well
我们也将jdk设为9jk 9
very shortly well that doesn't sound too
很快，听起来也不太好
bad maybe it will go smoother than we
不好，也许会比我们更顺畅
expected but that's this hold for the
预期的，但是这对于
entire ecosystem what do you think how
整个生态系统你怎么看
it will be impacted so I think John is
它会受到影响，所以我认为约翰是
going to it will change the ecosystem
去它会改变生态系统
and the wider job community in two ways
和更广泛的工作社区有两种方式
the first way is I think it's the first
第一种方式是我认为这是第一种
step into a new kind of Java room first
首先进入一种新的Java室
of all the module system will be will be
所有模块系统将是
at the very center of us being able to
在我们的中心
change things faster in Java in the
在Java中更快地改变事物
future so that that's the first thing
未来，那是第一件事
it's not quite there yet but it's the
它还不在那里，但是
first step certainly the second thing I
第一步当然是第二件事
think how it's going to change the Java
想想它将如何改变Java
ecosystem is every library tall
生态系统每个图书馆都很高
framework app server everyone is going
框架应用服务器的每个人都在前进
to need to make sure they support
需要确保他们支持
applications that want to use the module
想要使用模块的应用程序
system whether that's turning their
系统是否正在转向他们
libraries frameworks tools into kind of
库框架工具
automatic modules that couldn't that can
不能的自动模块
be used by an application or whether
由应用程序使用还是
they choose to go full the full duration
他们选择全程
and motorize themselves with module in
并使用模块中的
photo op classes and you know change
摄影班，你知道改变
them turn themselves into negative named
他们把自己变成负面的名字
modules that's entirely up to them but
模块完全取决于他们，但是
the entire Java community is going to
整个Java社区将
need to need to step up and make sure
需要加强并确保
they support your knowing for sure so I
他们肯定支持您的了解，所以我
think there's no doubt that Java none
认为毫无疑问，Java没有
will cause some problems in the wider
会在更大范围内引起一些问题
community it's you know it's a major
社区，这是你的专业
release it introduces a big view feature
发布它引入了大视野功能
and fundamentally it's the hacks that
从根本上说，就是骇客
we've all been using for the past 20
过去20年来我们一直在使用
years
年份
many of these hacks are going to be
这些黑客中的许多将
closed off now this is good for the long
现在关门了
term but will undoubtably cause us some
学期，但无疑会导致我们一些
pain in the short term yeah it's a tough
短期内是痛苦的，是的，这很难
one that's not easy to answer the module
一个不容易回答的模块
system pack some of migration features
系统打包了一些迁移功能
so in theory it should be possible for
因此从理论上讲
the entire community for the entire
整个社区
ecosystem to modularize incrementally
生态系统逐步模块化
every project at their own pace but
每个项目都按照自己的进度
that's kind of like an ideal and it's
这有点像理想，
not it's not quite obvious where that
不是很明显
work exactly like that so what I'm sure
完全像那样工作，所以我确定
that there will not be a schism like
不会有像这样的分裂
between Python 2 and 3
在Python 2和3之间
- in Java eight in Java nine it's not
-在Java 8中，在Java 9中不是
impossible that there will be more
不可能会有更多
reservations to updating to Java nine
保留更新到Java 9
than the war when updating to Java eight
比战争当升级到Java八
in terms of the wider community jigsaw
就更广泛的社区拼图而言
has the potential to have quite a big
有很大的潜力
impact on the way that we developed
对我们发展方式的影响
libraries the way that we consume other
以我们消费其他方式的方式
code and so I'm really interested to see
代码，所以我真的很感兴趣
what's going to happen there as it is
那里会发生什么
I'm not really sure exactly how quickly
我不太确定到底能多快
this is going to be adopted but I think
这将被采用，但我认为
it's going to be very interesting with
这将是非常有趣的
the release of Java 9 the ball is now in
Java 9的发布现已开始
the corner of the java community do we
我们在Java社区的角落
value what software developments I
重视我开发的软件
especially want to encourage library
特别想鼓励图书馆
maintains to adopt the module system so
保持采用模块系统
we as application developers can all
作为应用程序开发人员，我们可以
benefit in the long run it took years
从长远来看，从中受益
and years for just the API the JRE to
JRE所用的API的年限和
get optimized right to get modular so I
得到优化以获得模块化的权利，所以我
don't see many people jumping in and
没有看到很多人跳进去
modernizing their current applications
现代化其当前的应用程序
but I see it the long-term benefit is
但我看到它的长期利益是
that modularity is is going to open up
模块化将要开放
the understanding as well as the
的理解以及
dependencies and and correlations and
依赖性和相关性以及
between the libraries and everything so
在图书馆和一切之间
it's going to benefit the entire
这将使整个国家受益
ecosystem in the long run on the long
从长远来看生态系统
term I hope that ma little modularity is
学期，我希望有点模块化
basically accepted as a general concept
基本上被接受为一般概念
and that more libraries migrated but I
而且更多的图书馆迁移了，但是我
also think that a lot of libraries will
也认为很多图书馆会
die off over time because many libraries
随着时间的流逝，死了，因为许多图书馆
aren't really maintained anymore they're
真的不再维护了
still used today because they can be
至今仍在使用，因为它们可以
used today but I think those libraries
今天用过，但我认为那些图书馆
that don't have much support anymore
不再有太多支持了
will just disappear maybe that's a good
会消失，也许那是一个好习惯
thing as well so shouldn't you new
东西，所以你不应该新
libraries can grow in this context and
图书馆可以在这种情况下发展壮大，
yeah I'm excited to see what happens
是的，我很高兴看到发生了什么
then I'm not all that sure what sort of
那我就不确定
direct impact that John tonight itself
约翰今晚本身的直接影响
will have on the wider Java community I
我将在更广泛的Java社区中拥有
am curious to see what sort of real
很想知道什么样的真实
adoption we'll see by that community
该社区将看到的采用率
regardless the cleanup work that came
不管接下来的清理工作
before Java 9 it one tangle the core
在Java 9之前，它纠结了核心
libraries to make modularization even
库使模块化甚至
possible was necessary work that in
可能有必要的工作
itself extends the life of Java it'll
本身可以延长Java的寿命
certainly be interesting to see what the
一定很有趣，看看
wider community decides to do with
更广泛的社区决定与
modules who will for example offer their
例如谁将提供他们的模块
code
码
module form time will tell I think JDK 9
模块形式的时间会告诉我我认为JDK 9
is going to have a big impact and the
将会产生很大的影响，
biggest thing is making sure that
最大的事情是确保
people's code runs on JDK 9 because of
人们的代码在JDK 9上运行是因为
the encapsulation of the various
各种封装
non-public api's in the JDK and the
JDK和
impact that has especially when you're
尤其在您
using frameworks or third-party
使用框架或第三方
libraries which are using things like
使用诸如
some misconception you might not be
一些误解，你可能不是
aware of that obviously there are
意识到显然有
command-line options which will enable
命令行选项将启用
you to make that transition easier but
您可以使过渡更容易，但是
it is going to have quite a big impact
这将产生很大的影响
as people make that move to using JDK 9
人们开始使用JDK 9
and ensuring that their code runs on
并确保其代码在
that without any problems
没有任何问题
the other thing I'd mention is that
我要提到的另一件事是
there's a lot of command-line options
有很多命令行选项
the - xx ones that have changed between
-xx个在
JDK 8 and JDK 9 and that's something
JDK 8和JDK 9就是这样
that people will have to adjust to as
人们将不得不适应
well sounds like the community needs to
听起来好像社区需要
step up its game and really learn about
加强游戏，真正了解
modularity and compatibility challenges
模块化和兼容性挑战
any good sources you could recommend
您可以推荐的任何好的资源
I'll give you an option of - - books
我给你一个选择--书籍
around Java modularity and jigsaw the
围绕Java模块化和拼图
first by Nicola Pollock the Java module
首先是Nicola Pollock的Java模块
system book by Manning the second one is
曼宁的系统书第二本是
actually one that I reviewed myself so I
实际上是我自己回顾过的一个，所以我
know it's a great book it's called the
知道这是一本很棒的书，叫做
Java 9 it's called Java 9 modularity
Java 9，称为Java 9模块化
it's no Riley book and that's by Paul
这不是莱利的书，那是保罗的
Becker and sand and Mac so both I'm sure
贝克尔，沙和Mac，所以我都相信
going to be good books and I think
将会是好书，我认为
everyone every developer really needs to
每个开发人员真正需要的每个人
learn and understand what's coming in
学习并了解即将发生的事情
Java 9 and beyond with the module system
Java 9及更高版本的模块系统
and the module part it's going to be
还有模块部分
something which is going to effects all
将会影响所有人的东西
and something which I think it's
我认为这是
important for all developers to
对所有开发人员来说都很重要
understand so one thing you can look for
了解，所以你可以寻找一件事
on Java 9 is my blog on module names and
在Java 9上是我关于模块名称的博客，
what exactly a module is and how it
确切的模块是什么以及如何
differs from an artifact you know what
不同于人工制品，你知道
I'm gonna say right good book get book
我要说正确的好书得到书
you should definitely check out my
你一定要看看我的
real-world Java 9 presentation in it I
我在其中的实际Java 9演示文稿
tries to give a live demo of the sorts
尝试进行现场演示
of features in Java 9 that we're
Java 9中的一些功能
actually going to use obviously I'd like
实际上，显然我要使用
you also read my book Jaafar know
您还读了我的书《 Jaafar》
modularity which was recently completed
最近完成的模块化
and released by Ronnie as an organizer
由Ronnie作为组织者发布
of dollars and I of course have to
美元，我当然要
mention our videos that we put our dried
提到我们放干的视频
after the conference
会议结束后
it's very up to date talks about newest
关于最新的最新话题
things to come out if you're curious to
如果您想知道会发生什么
see what it's taken to implement support
了解实现支持需要采取的措施
for Java 9 including an independent
适用于Java 9，包括独立的
open-source implementation of the
的开源实现
compiler check out wiki dot eclipse.org
编译器签出wiki dot eclipse.org
slash uppercase J Java 9 I'm gonna blow
大写的J Java 9我要打击
my own trumpet here and I'm gonna say
我自己的喇叭在这里，我要说
that there's there's several things I've
我有几件事
done which I think are quite useful you
我认为对您很有用
can find on YouTube I've done a
可以在YouTube上找到我已经完成的
presentation called 55 new features in
演示文稿中的55个新功能
JDK 9 at a number of conferences and
JDK 9在许多会议和
more recently I've written a couple of
最近我写了几本书
blog entries which people will probably
人们可能会写的博客条目
find it useful
觉得有用
one of which relates back to the answer
其中之一与答案有关
to the previous question which is where
上一个问题在哪里
I've looked at the changes in terms of
我从以下方面看了变化
command lines in fact I did a whole blog
命令行事实上我做了一个整个博客
on all the incompatible changes between
之间的所有不兼容的变化
JDK 8 and JDK 9 I think people would
我认为人们会选择JDK 8和JDK 9
probably find that very useful oh you're
可能会发现它非常有用哦
back already let me just put this
回来已经让我把这个
somewhere to wrap it up I asked my
某个地方把它包起来，我问我的
guests well if they wanted to thank the
客人很好，如果他们想感谢
JDK team and oh boy didn't they so this
JDK团队和哦，男孩，他们不是这样的
is for you JDK engineers out there so
是给您的JDK工程师
you can bask in the well-earned glory of
你可以沐浴在来之不易的荣耀中
your hard work I think mark Reinhold did
你的辛苦，我认为马克·莱因霍德（Mark Reinhold）做过
a lot of good work in in you know
你知道很多好的工作
heeding the advice of the ecosystem and
留意生态系统的建议
working to make sure that Java 9 was in
努力确保Java 9在
a better State for adoption by the
一个更好的国家供采纳
ecosystem big thanks to the JDK team
JDK团队非常感谢生态系统
have worked very hard on the Java 9
在Java 9方面非常努力
release modules is a tricky problem and
发布模块是一个棘手的问题，
we've come up with a solution I think in
我们想出了一个解决方案
the end that that while hard in the
最后，虽然努力
short term will work history like
短期内会像
Reinholds and abatement Alex Buckley as
保留和减轻亚历克斯·巴克利（Alex Buckley）作为
I see it those three have been the first
我看到那三个是第一个
line of the modern system efforts but
现代系统努力的路线，但是
I'm sure they're not being the only ones
我敢肯定他们不是唯一的人
right so I want to thank all the unsung
对，所以我要感谢所有默默无闻的人
heroes who've done work in the
在
backgrounds I'm sure participate in lots
我肯定会参加很多背景
to make the model system after almost 10
在将近10个模型后制作模型系统
years finally come to the Java ecosystem
年终于来到Java生态系统
in Java 9 thank you so much I want to
在Java 9中非常感谢我想
thank the whole JK team for all their
感谢整个JK团队的所有努力
hard work on this release it's taken a
在这个版本上的辛苦工作
while to get out but it must have been
虽然要出去，但一定是
so hard to work on it and they've been
如此努力工作，他们一直
really responsive to any questions that
真正回应任何问题
we have any feedback from the community
我们有任何来自社区的反馈
and they've taken the time to listen to
他们花了时间听
us and to make changes to the language
我们并改变语言
which will actually
实际上
which will actually help I think this is
这实际上会帮助我认为这是
fantastic thank you so much
太好了，谢谢你
[Music]
[音乐]
I definitely have to thank Mark Reynolds
我一定要感谢马克·雷诺兹
for for taking me not too bad with all
为了让我对一切都不太糟
my opinions so I think that is sometimes
我的意见，所以我认为有时候
not not easy I guess the other way
不容易，我想换一种方式
around as well so he did a great job the
周围也是如此，所以他做得很好
module system is is a big step for the
模块系统对于
JDK itself it was a necessary step so
JDK本身是必需的步骤，因此
and obviously all of the other guys had
显然所有其他人都有
worked on Java 9 Brian guts John Rose I
从事Java 9 Brian胆量John Rose I的工作
don't think you can you can single out
不要以为可以挑出来
some very specific person I'd like to
我想要一些非常具体的人
thank Alex Berkeley and Ellen Bateman
感谢Alex Berkeley和Ellen Bateman
from the JDK see both our key players in
从JDK中可以看到我们两个主要参与者
the implementation of the module system
模块系统的实施
in Java night but they've also
在JAVA之夜，但他们也
graciously taken time to service
亲切的服务时间
technical reviewers for the Javan 9
Javan 9的技术评审员
modularity book thanks guys
模块化书谢谢大家
I was a part of the performance team the
我是表演团队的一员
JDK performance team so I would like to
JDK性能团队，所以我想
thank everybody in the performance team
感谢表演团队中的每个人
for for doing a great job with Java 9
用于在Java 9中出色地完成工作
release Vladimir's loss from the
释放弗拉基米尔的损失
compiler team for IOT work that he's
他从事物联网工作的编译器团队
done and so many others and all the
完成，还有很多其他的事情
developers thank you very much really
开发人员真的非常感谢你
appreciate all the hard work yeah I
感谢所有的辛勤工作，是的，我
think I want to thank Mark Reinhold he
想我要感谢马克·莱因霍尔德他
really held out there you got a lot of
真的在那里，你有很多
criticism may be partly deserved but
批评可能是部分应得的，但
also undeserved often and he really
也经常不配，他真的
pushed through and took into
推了进去
consideration what people are concerned
考虑人们在关注什么
about I think he really did a good job
我认为他确实做得很好
there and can thank him for for getting
在那里，并感谢他获得
this job done jigsaw was a hard project
拼图完成的这项工作是一个艰巨的项目
yeah I think that there's there's a lot
是的，我认为那里有很多
of people who've been involved in JJ 9
参与《 JJ 9》的人
and it's it's probably wrong to a single
这可能是一个人的错
out one particular person but in this
淘汰一个特定的人
case I think one particular person does
我觉得一个人的情况
need to be singled out and that's not
需要被挑出来，那不是
right hold you have to do him credit for
权利持有，你必须为他效劳
sticking with it for so long and finally
坚持了这么久，最后
getting modularity done finally getting
最终完成模块化
modularity into the JDK so I take my
模块化进入JDK，所以我把我的
head off the mark and his perseverance
勇往直前和他的毅力
for getting this actually through and
为了使这个通过
finally out into the wild it's all great
终于荒野了，一切都很棒
guide words got me all cheered up ok
指导词让我都很高兴
that's it for today thanks again to the
今天就是这样，再次感谢
awesome people who took part in this
很棒的人参加了
video make sure to follow them on
视频，请确保跟随他们
Twitter or check out their links which
Twitter或查看他们的链接
are put into the description box
放在说明框中
and if you want to see more videos about
如果您想观看更多有关的视频
software development JVM and Java make
软件开发JVM和Java make
sure to subscribe to this channel or
一定要订阅此频道或
follow me on twitter where Patni
在推特上关注我
Pathak's so long
帕塔克这么长
welcome job knowing it's a pleasure to
欢迎工作，知道这很高兴
finally get you Java 9 here we go hats
终于让您Java 9到这里了
leash with comments online I for one
在网上用评论拴住我一个
welcome our Java 9 overlords finally
终于欢迎我们的Java 9霸主
Java 9 is here I'm looking forward to
Java 9在这里，我期待着
1903 hey dojo 9 I think we've waited
1903年嘿道场9我想我们已经等了
long enough now and good luck with the
现在足够长的时间，祝你好运
ticks all about time Joe 9
滴答滴答地打发时间Joe 9
welcome Java 9 welcome JDK 9
欢迎Java 9欢迎JDK 9
ah
啊